{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/4168","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4168","name":"Star Life Bar & Grill","address":"18300 Seven Mile Rd. W.","zipcode":"48219","owner":"Christine Renfro","licenseNumber":"255119","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-83.22198,42.43024","geojson":{"id":"4168","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.221975328,42.430237732]},"properties":{"name":"Star Life Bar & Grill","owner":"Christine Renfro","address":"18300 Seven Mile Rd. W.","zipcode":"48219","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"255119","establishmentid":"4168","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":"2021-03-17"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622494","name":"Saxony Lounge","address":"18300 W. Seven Mile Rd.","zipcode":"48219"},{"establishmentid":"3983","name":"Club XO","address":"18300 Seven Mile Rd. W.","zipcode":"48219"},{"establishmentid":"51623694","name":"Club Toxic LLC","address":"18300 Seven Mile W.","zipcode":"48219"},{"establishmentid":"205","name":"Saxony's Lounge","address":"18300 Seven Mile Rd. W.","zipcode":"48219"},{"establishmentid":"1305","name":"Teenie's Deli Inc.","address":"18244 Seven Mile Rd. W.","zipcode":"48219"},{"establishmentid":"2364","name":"Woody's Wild Wings","address":"18239 Seven Mile Rd. W.","zipcode":"48219"},{"establishmentid":"51623022","name":"The Sleepy Potato (Illegal Establishment","address":"18216 W. 7 Mile Rd.","zipcode":"48219"},{"establishmentid":"3229","name":"J & G Soul Food","address":"18216 Seven Mile Rd. W.","zipcode":"48219"},{"establishmentid":"1267","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #991","address":"18138 Seven Mile Rd. W.","zipcode":"48219"},{"establishmentid":"51622856","name":"T.A. Krispy Chicken","address":"18525 W. Seven Mile Rd.","zipcode":"48219"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"40470","inspectionDate":"2017-07-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"between drain line and flood rim of receiving drain","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Raw ready-to-eat food(s) Vegetable(s)","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-07-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink kitchen","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-07-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-07-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"in ladies restroom","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"ceiling(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"40468","inspectionDate":"2016-10-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink bar","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-10-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-10-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."}]},{"inspectionid":"36609","inspectionDate":"2016-09-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-10-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink bar","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-10-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4168"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}